I am Oluwatobiloba Bamisebi Oluwatobiofficial15@gmail.com

https://github.com/oluwatobiloba1

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY-

Software developer dedicated to helping clients accomplish technical goals by developing user-friendly and forward-thinking apps. Experience working using modern tools in building fully functional web apps and aesthetic Web pages. Quality-focused developer with a history of working well in fast-paced, challenging, and team-oriented environments.

EDUCATION -

Senior secondary school

2015

Federal science and technical college, Lagos state Yaba, Nigeria.

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Industrial Mathematics with computer science University of Lagos, Lagos state Yaba, Nigeria.

2023

WORK EXPERIENCE-

BACKEND DEVELOPER

September 2023 – October 2023

@ HNG[x] internship

- Assisted a small team of front-end and back-end developers with building multiple internal applications using Next is and Typescript.
- Deployed and hosted on remote servers
- Documented some important processes in the whole development cycle of the SASS.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

October 2023 - June 2024

- @ GreaterEredo Nigeria @agrictrail
 - Worked with a team of developers to build multiple internal dashboard applications using Next js and Typescript.
 - API integration with graphql models
 - Documented some important processes in the whole development cycle of the SASS.

BACKEND DEVELOPER

October 2023 - June 2024

- @ Prodeegi Veesitor.com
 - Worked with a small team consisting of (Mobile Developer, Product Designer, and a Product Manager)
 - Job description involved building APIs for consumption on the frontend, using Nestjs and Mongodb Database.
 - Documentation for API integration.

TECHNICAL SKILLS -

- Computing: JavaScript, Typescript, NodeJs, ReactJs/Nextjs, Python, Microsoft Office Suite, Google Suite, Learning Go
- **Professional:** Problem Solving, Critical Thinking,
- Languages: English (fluent)

ACTIVITIES—

- Certificate of completion of responsive web development course by freeCodeCamp.
 - o freeCodeCamp certification